[{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664185963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":41632,"timeElapsed":171850},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664205536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":19568,"timeElapsed":191422},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664231269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":25725,"timeElapsed":217155},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664263345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":32071,"timeElapsed":249232},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":13453,"timeElapsed":262689},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664288580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":11772,"timeElapsed":274466},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664297814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9230,"timeElapsed":283700},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664326773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":28956,"timeElapsed":312659},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664337905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11129,"timeElapsed":323792},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664356141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":15287,"timeElapsed":342027},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664367881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":11737,"timeElapsed":353768},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664385507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":17624,"timeElapsed":371394},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664396168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":10658,"timeElapsed":382055},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664421780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":25607,"timeElapsed":407666},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664431289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":9506,"timeElapsed":417176},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664444897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":13605,"timeElapsed":430784},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664453296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8396,"timeElapsed":439183},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664463574,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10273,"timeElapsed":449461},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664474126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10547,"timeElapsed":460012},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664528414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":50313,"timeElapsed":514301},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664548009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":19592,"timeElapsed":533896},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664560892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12879,"timeElapsed":546779},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664567508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6613,"timeElapsed":553395},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664583844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":16331,"timeElapsed":569731},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664589364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5517,"timeElapsed":575251},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664603057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13690,"timeElapsed":588944},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664617576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14517,"timeElapsed":603463},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664628647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11069,"timeElapsed":614534},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664643395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":12501,"timeElapsed":629282},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664656291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":12891,"timeElapsed":642178},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664693809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":37516,"timeElapsed":679696},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664704046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":10234,"timeElapsed":689933},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664714359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":10309,"timeElapsed":700245},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664722070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":7707,"timeElapsed":707956},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664727276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":5202,"timeElapsed":713162},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664751973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":24693,"timeElapsed":737859},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664761015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":9039,"timeElapsed":746902},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664778775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":15649,"timeElapsed":764662},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664786462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":7684,"timeElapsed":772348},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664799539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":13075,"timeElapsed":785426},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664844943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":45400,"timeElapsed":830830},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664850688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5743,"timeElapsed":836575},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664856109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5416,"timeElapsed":841995},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664863828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":7716,"timeElapsed":849714},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664881280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":17450,"timeElapsed":867167},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664889072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":7787,"timeElapsed":874958},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664917293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":26852,"timeElapsed":903180},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664929136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":11840,"timeElapsed":915023},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664991087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":61947,"timeElapsed":976974},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664998123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7031,"timeElapsed":984010},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665005127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":7001,"timeElapsed":991014},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665009145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":4015,"timeElapsed":995032},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665015759,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6610,"timeElapsed":1001645},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665024463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":8701,"timeElapsed":1010349},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665036761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":12295,"timeElapsed":1022647},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665044531,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":7768,"timeElapsed":1030418},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665073843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":27886,"timeElapsed":1059730},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665082800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8954,"timeElapsed":1068687},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665089859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7058,"timeElapsed":1075746},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665100133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":10272,"timeElapsed":1086020},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665105193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":5057,"timeElapsed":1091080},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665111307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":6112,"timeElapsed":1097194},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665117048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":5737,"timeElapsed":1102934},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665125571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":8520,"timeElapsed":1111458},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665131421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5846,"timeElapsed":1117308},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665144507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":11304,"timeElapsed":1130394},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665150735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6224,"timeElapsed":1136622},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665163587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":12846,"timeElapsed":1149474},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665169634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":6043,"timeElapsed":1155521},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665174239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4600,"timeElapsed":1160125},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665179263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5018,"timeElapsed":1165150},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665183866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4600,"timeElapsed":1169753},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665198435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":14566,"timeElapsed":1184321},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665203210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4773,"timeElapsed":1189097},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665222314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":17602,"timeElapsed":1208200},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665245161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":22845,"timeElapsed":1231048},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665254150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":8986,"timeElapsed":1240037},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665261252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":7099,"timeElapsed":1247139},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665265285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4030,"timeElapsed":1251172},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665272196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6906,"timeElapsed":1258083},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665278148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":5948,"timeElapsed":1264035},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665287263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":9112,"timeElapsed":1273149},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665297885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":10619,"timeElapsed":1283772},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665318047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":18723,"timeElapsed":1303934},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665325010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":6959,"timeElapsed":1310897},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665346660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":21647,"timeElapsed":1332547},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665351963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5301,"timeElapsed":1337850},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665358318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6352,"timeElapsed":1344205},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665363261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4940,"timeElapsed":1349147},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665368994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5729,"timeElapsed":1354881},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665381738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":12741,"timeElapsed":1367625},{"subjectID":"uv3t4q3gj1","prolificID":"67279fa0368ebc801eb5817a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742169bf8a434754bdc601","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665386536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4794,"timeElapsed":1372423}]